intoxicatedonlife.com 2019-09-28

# Disclosure & Privacy Policy for IntoxicatedOnLife.com

### FTC Disclosure Statement

At intoxicatedonlife.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by intoxicatedonlife.com and how it is used.

As the owner of this blog we have the full intention to be compliant with the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) rules about the use of testimonials and endorsements in advertising and marketing. I want you as a visitor to understand that at times I get paid a commission to endorse products or services on my site. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. If you have a question about whether or not I’m connected with anything I promote or endorse, please [contact us](https://intoxicatedonlife.com/about-us/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Intoxicatedonlife.com does not use cookies.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, intoxicatedonlife.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Amazon.com

Intoxicatedonlife.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees. We get paid a commission for each item you purchase in a session on Amazon.com when you click through an Amazon widget or link on my site. This is a part of the normal Amazon.com affiliate program.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on intoxicatedonlife.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to intoxicatedonlife.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on intoxicatedonlife.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Intoxicatedonlife.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Intoxicatedonlife.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

This blog does not share personal information with third parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this blog other than to analyze and optimize your content and reading experience through the use of cookies.

We are not responsible for republished content from this blog on other blogs or websites without our permission.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on February, 8, 2013. If you have any questions feel free to [contact us](https://intoxicatedonlife.com/about-us/contact-us/ "Contact Us") directly.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

### Information Collected

Intoxicated on Life’s online store collects names, credit card information, and email addresses to process payments. This information is never shared, rented, and sold to third parties
